<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.17">
  <compounddef id="namespacerecharge" kind="namespace" language="Python">
    <compoundname>recharge</compoundname>
    <innerclass refid="classrecharge_1_1_recharge" prot="public">recharge::Recharge</innerclass>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><verbatim>.. module:: recahrge
    :platform: ROS
    :synopsis: Class for Recharge state of the finite state machine

.. moduleauthor:: Matteo Maragliano 4636216@studenti.unitge.it

This class represent the recharging state of the finite state machine. This state is executed every time the battery of the robot is low and the robot is located in the recharging room.
In particular, if the robot is in a location and it can reach the recharging room then the FSM enters in this state, brings the robot to the recharging room and then recharges it.
If the robot is in a location and it cannot reach the recharging room this state is not executed because the robot could not physically enter in the rechargin location.
At the end if the robot is already in the recharging location then the recharging state just recharges the robot and returns an execute action that allows the program know the robot can start again moving randonmly.
The recharging method takes more or less 5 seconds to recharge the robot completely to 100% before let it go away again.
The movement or the robot is performed thanks to the :mod:`planner` and the :mod:`controller` through a request to the servers by the clients used.
The location of the robot is checked by a query by the aRMOR client and its respective server.
The clients are taken from the helper object initialized in the state.

Clients:
    :attr:`client`: aRMOR client used to update the timestamp of the robot and of the location the robot has just visited
    
    :attr:`planner_client`: client from which it is taken the goal, which means the path just computed to be passed to the controller.
    
    :attr:`controller_client`: client that makes the request to the respective server to move the robot through the path from the starting to the end position.
</verbatim> </para>
    </detaileddescription>
    <location file="/root/ros_ws/src/EXPROBLAB_Assignment2/scripts/recharge.py" line="1" column="1"/>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
